{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Stone \u0026 Granite Countertop Repair Pros","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40200/":{"taskOID":40200,"originalTaskOID":40200,"setID":507,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5111,"questionDisplayText":"Damage Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the best description(s) of the countertop repair you need. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5501,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Scratched","answerDisplayText":"Scratched","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1689,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Cracked","answerDisplayText":"Cracked","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1383,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Chipped","answerDisplayText":"Chipped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2113,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Dull/Hazy","answerDisplayText":"Dull/Hazy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1946,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Discolored/Stained","answerDisplayText":"Discolored/Stained","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1693,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Cracked grout","answerDisplayText":"Cracked grout","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4070,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Need polishing","answerDisplayText":"Need polishing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4098,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Needs cleaning","answerDisplayText":"Needs cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4113,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Needs sealing","answerDisplayText":"Needs sealing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5105,"questionDisplayText":"Countertop Style","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of natural stone countertop do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2837,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Granite","answerDisplayText":"Granite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Marble","answerDisplayText":"Marble","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4987,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Quartz","answerDisplayText":"Quartz","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5776,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Slate","answerDisplayText":"Slate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3611,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Limestone","answerDisplayText":"Limestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2500,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Flagstone","answerDisplayText":"Flagstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5844,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Soapstone","answerDisplayText":"Soapstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500649,"questionDisplayText":"Type of countertop","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of countertop is it?","shortQuestionText":"What type of countertop is it?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4380,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One solid piece of stone","answerDisplayText":"One solid piece of stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6107,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stone tiles","answerDisplayText":"Stone tiles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5111,"questionDisplayText":"Damage Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the best description(s) of the countertop repair you need. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5501,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Scratched","answerDisplayText":"Scratched","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1689,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Cracked","answerDisplayText":"Cracked","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1383,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Chipped","answerDisplayText":"Chipped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2113,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Dull/Hazy","answerDisplayText":"Dull/Hazy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1946,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Discolored/Stained","answerDisplayText":"Discolored/Stained","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1693,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Cracked grout","answerDisplayText":"Cracked grout","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4070,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Need polishing","answerDisplayText":"Need polishing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4098,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Needs cleaning","answerDisplayText":"Needs cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4113,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Needs sealing","answerDisplayText":"Needs sealing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5501,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Scratched","answerDisplayText":"Scratched","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1689,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Cracked","answerDisplayText":"Cracked","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1383,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Chipped","answerDisplayText":"Chipped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2113,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Dull/Hazy","answerDisplayText":"Dull/Hazy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1946,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Discolored/Stained","answerDisplayText":"Discolored/Stained","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1693,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Cracked grout","answerDisplayText":"Cracked grout","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4070,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Need polishing","answerDisplayText":"Need polishing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4098,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Needs cleaning","answerDisplayText":"Needs cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4113,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Needs sealing","answerDisplayText":"Needs sealing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5105,"questionDisplayText":"Countertop Style","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of natural stone countertop do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2837,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Granite","answerDisplayText":"Granite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Marble","answerDisplayText":"Marble","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4987,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Quartz","answerDisplayText":"Quartz","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5776,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Slate","answerDisplayText":"Slate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3611,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Limestone","answerDisplayText":"Limestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2500,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Flagstone","answerDisplayText":"Flagstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5844,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Soapstone","answerDisplayText":"Soapstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2837,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Granite","answerDisplayText":"Granite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Marble","answerDisplayText":"Marble","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4987,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Quartz","answerDisplayText":"Quartz","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5776,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Slate","answerDisplayText":"Slate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3611,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Limestone","answerDisplayText":"Limestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2500,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Flagstone","answerDisplayText":"Flagstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5844,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Soapstone","answerDisplayText":"Soapstone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500649,"questionDisplayText":"Type of countertop","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of countertop is it?","shortQuestionText":"What type of countertop is it?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4380,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One solid piece of stone","answerDisplayText":"One solid piece of stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6107,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stone tiles","answerDisplayText":"Stone tiles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4380,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One solid piece of stone","answerDisplayText":"One solid piece of stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6107,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stone tiles","answerDisplayText":"Stone tiles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40200/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40200,"taskName":"Stone Slab Countertops - Repair (Granite, Marble, Quartz, etc)","taskDescription":"Repair Stone Slab Countertops","xmTaskDescriptor":"Stone \u0026 Granite Countertop Repair Pros","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":52,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"counter corian counters tile tops","textMessagingName":"Repr Stone Counters","rolloverLongDesc":"In general, stone cannot be repaired. However, when pieces of stone are out of alignment or when the homeowner seeks to replace or add-on a section of countertop, hearth or mantel, this category is appropriate. These firms have experience with modifying existing work \u0026 attempting to match stone colors \u0026 patterns.","rolloverShortDesc":"Realign, augment or reset solid stone surfaces.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Stone Slab Countertops.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Stone \u0026 Granite Countertop Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix Quartz, Marble Countertops, Stone Slabs","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":8,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Stone Slab Countertop Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Stone Slab Countertops - Repair (Granite, Marble, Quartz, etc)","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Stone Slab Countertop Project","urlName":"Stone-Slab-Marble-Countertops-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Stone/Granite Countertop Repair Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Quartz, Marble Counter Repair","searchKeywords":"counter,corian,counters,tile,tops,countertop,top","emcCategoryOid":-12016,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":507,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}